<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Botahamec</title>
    <link>https://botahamec.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Botahamec</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 15:57:43 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://botahamec.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trolley Problem Memes, Explained</title>
      <link>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_07_08_trolley_problem_memes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 15:57:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_07_08_trolley_problem_memes/</guid>
      <description>Several Trolley Problem Memes, Explained You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard of the Trolley Problem, if not let me explain.
The Trolley Problem, Explained There&amp;rsquo;s a trolley charging down the tracks. It&amp;rsquo;s heading towards a path with five people on it. If nothing is done, these people will surely be doomed.
GOOD NEWS! There just happens to be a lever which switch the tracks to a different path, thus causing the train to miss five people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Was Kira Right?</title>
      <link>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_06_27_death_note/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:57:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_06_27_death_note/</guid>
      <description>Last semester, I took a class called, Intro to Moral Issues. One of the assignments we did was a &amp;ldquo;Contemporary Controversy&amp;rdquo;. Each person in the class had to pick a philosophical or political topic and write an essay to convince the class of their position. The professor made it clear that topics relating to media are allowed1.
As it happened, the week before I found out about this, I became curious and read all of the rules of the Death Note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police Brutality</title>
      <link>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_06_04_justice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:37:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_06_04_justice/</guid>
      <description>This article is a mess. Sorry.
Background Initially, I was planning on skipping this part. Partly because I figured everyone would know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about, and partly because I don&amp;rsquo;t really know how to explain it. Although, people reading this in the future will probably need an explanation, so here it is. Instead of explaining it myself, I&amp;rsquo;ll let others explain it for me. Here&amp;rsquo;s a bunch of videos you can watch:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas for Projects to Do</title>
      <link>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_06_03_project_ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:13:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_06_03_project_ideas/</guid>
      <description>I have a lot of ideas for future projects. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably never get to do most of them. So let me list some of them so that you may give them a try.
Sudoku Solver Yes, I know many people have done this already. I really like the idea though so I wanna try it without looking at other people&amp;rsquo;s solutions. Of course, you&amp;rsquo;re free to do it in whatever way you like, but you&amp;rsquo;ll probably need a GUI for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website! Hooray!</title>
      <link>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_06_02_new_site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 10:13:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://botahamec.github.io/posts/20_06_02_new_site/</guid>
      <description>Hello, everyone! Welcome to my new site. If you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the old one, then you know that looked remarkably terrible. Not only did it look like a dump, it was horrible to work with. Have you ever tried doing pure HTML code blocks? It&amp;rsquo;s a pain. Now that issue is fixed by using MARKDOWN! Look at this:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15  fn main() { const MAX_NUM = 40; let mut a = 0; let mut b = 1; let mut c; for _i in 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chalk-rs</title>
      <link>https://botahamec.github.io/projects/chalk_rs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://botahamec.github.io/projects/chalk_rs/</guid>
      <description>A crate for terminal colors and styles
1 2 3 4  use chalk_rs::Chalk; let mut chalk = Chalk::new(); chalk.red().println(&amp;amp;&amp;#34;This text is red&amp;#34;); chalk.bold().println(&amp;amp;&amp;#34;Now it&amp;#39;s red AND bold&amp;#34;);   That&amp;rsquo;s an example of basic color. There are three types of color in chalk: BasicChalk, AnsiChalk, and RgbChalk.
1 2 3 4  use chalk_rs::Chalk; let mut chalk = Chalk::new(); chalk.ansi(56).println(&amp;amp;&amp;#34;Purple-ish&amp;#34;); chalk.rgb(25, 125, 63).println(&amp;amp;&amp;#34;This color is ugly&amp;#34;);   Chalk can aldo do styling!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pronoun Testing Grounds</title>
      <link>https://botahamec.github.io/projects/pronoun_test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://botahamec.github.io/projects/pronoun_test/</guid>
      <description>https://botahamec.github.io/pronoun_test
About This project was created for 43 North&amp;rsquo;s Code:Buffalo hackathon. It&amp;rsquo;s goal is to help people questioning their gender to try different sets of pronouns and see how they like them. This is similar to the technique of trying out names at Starbucks. It&amp;rsquo;s inspired by the Pronoun Dressing Room, which unfortunately has a limited number of stories. This version creates a new story each time.
How it Works The webpage uses HTML, CSS, and TypeScript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elp</title>
      <link>https://botahamec.github.io/projects/elp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://botahamec.github.io/projects/elp/</guid>
      <description>A helper for git to make some mundane tasks simpler. When you create an empty Github repository normally, you need to do five commands to get your local folder on the remote repository. This application simplifies things dramatically by giving commands which do these things for you automatically.
Building In order to build this, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have Cargo (the Rust compiler) and Git pre-installed.
 Clone the repository git clone https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>